<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Html on Chris Kirkland</title>
    <link>https://chriskirkland.github.io/chriskirkland.us/topics/html/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Html on Chris Kirkland</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 11:22:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chriskirkland.github.io/chriskirkland.us/topics/html/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cellular Automata (part 2)</title>
      <link>https://chriskirkland.github.io/chriskirkland.us/post/cellular-automata-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 11:22:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chriskirkland.github.io/chriskirkland.us/post/cellular-automata-updates/</guid>
      <description>Goal Around two months ago, I created a blog post for my weekend project demonstrating 1-dimensional Cellulator Automata; you can see that post here. Since then, I&amp;rsquo;ve started looking more into more current Web Development technologies including some of the videos from Travis Nielson&amp;rsquo;s fantastic youtube channel addressing topics in Web Development and full process design. Through those videos, I was introduced to the preprocessing/templating languages Pug (formerly Jade) and Sass for HTML and CSS, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>https://chriskirkland.github.io/chriskirkland.us/post/cellular-automata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 11:09:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chriskirkland.github.io/chriskirkland.us/post/cellular-automata/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration It has been several years since I&amp;rsquo;ve touched any front-end web technologies. Past projects included:
 Rebuilding the Mercer University Computer Science deparment website. Building a personal website for hosting syllabi, course materials, etc. while teaching in Grad school. This blog; built using Hugo which is technically cheating.  So recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for an excuse to brush up on JavaScript, in particular. The inspiration for this side project came from this video from MPJ&amp;rsquo;s popular series &amp;ldquo;Fun Fun Function&amp;rdquo;; if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any of his videos already, shame on you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>